Guide to the Edward Robb Ellis Papers ca. 1902-1998 MSS.068
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Media
  - December 31, 1971, ID: 068.0102 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0102)
    Audiocassette, Scotch 120 min.
  - June Morgan, Feb 24, 1974; June and Eddie, Feb. 25, 1974, ID: 068.0103 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0103)
  - Edward Ellis on radio, Feb 18, 1975 ([nobel] show), ID: 068.0104 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0104)
    Audiocassette, Memorex 90
  - June Morgan and Edward Ellis, Wed. Oct 1, 1975, ID: 068.0105 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0105)
    Audiocassette, Norelco C-90
  - Xmas '75- me, 1975; ID: 068.0106 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0106)
    Audiocassette, Tracs 90
  - June, Marcia, Eddie, July 22, 1976, ID: 068.0107 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0107)
  - Wad'ya know? Hour 1 with Michael Feldman 2/25/89 hr. 2 on side 2..., 1989; ID: 068.0108 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0108)
    Audiocassette, unknown brand, 60 min.
  - Ellis- BBC- 1991, ID: 068.0109 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0109)
    Audiocassette, JVC GI-90
  - Edward Robb ELlis Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, Feb. 11, 1991, ID: 068.0110 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0110)
    Audiocassette, TDK MA90
  - Ellis BBC, 1991, ID: 068.0111 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0111)
    Audiocassette, Unknown brand and length
  - Ellis BBC, 1991, ID: 068.0112 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0112)
    Audiocassette, Maxell XLI-S60
  - WNYC [NYELO] 10-2-95 Edward Robb Ellis, 1995; ID: 068.0113 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0113)
    Audiocassette, Unknown brand, C-60
  - NYELO 10-2-95, Edward Robb Ellis, 1995; ID: 068.0114 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0114)
    Audiocassette, TDK MA60
  - The Evening Talk Show with Glenn Mitchell Ellis, A Diary of the century, 13 December 1995 KERA 90.1 Dallas, Ft. Worth Denton, ID: 068.0115 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0115)
    Audiocassette, Unknown brand or length
  - Edward Robb Ellis, 7 March 1997, ID: 068.0116 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0116)
    Audiocassette, TDK D60
  - Afternoon with Mark Heimberger WDWS Champaign Illinois, thank you card included, undated; ID: 068.0117 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0117)
    Audiocassette, unknown brand or length
  - KPFK Edward Robb Ellis A Diary of the Century with Sylvia Maguite Pepper, undated; ID: 068.0118 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0118)
    Audiocassette, Maxell UR60
  - The Heywood Hale Broun Show with guests Roberta Feurelicht and Edward Robb Ellis, undated; ID: 068.0119 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0119)
  - Eddie Ellis on CBC, undated; ID: 068.0120 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0120)
    Audiocassette,TDK D60
  - Mango Theory, undated; ID: 068.0121 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0121)
    Audiocassette, TDK, unknown length
  - Friday Lives, BBC with Edward Robb Ellis, undated; ID: 068.0122 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0122)
    Audiocassette, Norelco 200 C-90
  - Eliz Irwan Locan 60 Colin St. Rochester, NY 14615, undated; ID: 068.0123 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0123)
    Audiocassette, Radio Shack Concertape 30
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 068.0124 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0124)
    Audiocassette, Sony HE60
  - Edward Ellis and World Panel, undated; ID: 068.0125 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0125)
    Audiocassette, Capitol 60
  - Messages to Myself, Margaret Wheeler, Reader: Elaine Claxton, undated; ID: 068.0126 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0126)
  - Friday Lives- BBC Edward Robb Ellis, undated; ID: 068.0127 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0127)
    Audiocassette, Memorex D60
  - Messages to Myself- Eva Marsh, Reader Shelley Tompson, undated; ID: 068.0128 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0128)
  - Messages to Myself- Sally Sedgman, Reader Amanda Redman, undated; ID: 068.0129 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0129)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 068.0130 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0130)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 068.0131 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0131)
  - Poems, undated; ID: 068.0132 (Box 51, Media ID: 068.0132)
    Audiocassette, Realistic C-30
  - Eddie Ellis on CBS-TV, Aug. 22, 1991, ID: 068.0133 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0133)
    VHS, Sony ES T120
  - Eddie Ellis 1991 Interviews, 3 copies in 2 folders, ID: 068.0134, 068.0135 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0134, 068.0135)
    VHS, BASF T120
  - Eddie Ellis 1991 Interviews, ID: 068.0136 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0136)
  - Eddie NY, November 13, 1995, ID: 068.0137 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0137)
    VHS, Maxell HGX Gold T120
  - Eddie Ellis, CBS Morning News, August 14, 1995, ID: 068.0138 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0138)
    VHS, TDK, unknown length
  - Eddie Ellis, Today Show (NBC), January 24, 1996; CBS This Morning, Good Morning America (ABC), September 4, 1995, 1995-1996; ID: 068.0139 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0139)
    VHS, TDK E-HG
  - Edward Robb Ellis NYU, November 13, 1996, ID: 068.0140 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0140)
    VHS, TDK EHG T120
  - A Diary of the Century Edward Robb Ellis on Good Morning America, undated; ID: 068.0141 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0141)
    VHS, Maxell
  - Eddie Ellis on Peter Jennings, ABC, February 21, 1996, ID: 068.0142 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0142)
    VHS, Maxell HGX-Gold T120
  - Ellis News Interviews, two copies, undated; ID: 068.0143 and 068.0144 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0143 and 068.0144)
    VHS, Funi high quality, T-120
  - News Interviews, undated; ID: 068.0145 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0145)
    VHS, Konica high performance E-30
  - Sallie O'D, undated; ID: 068.0146 (Box 52, Media ID: 068.0146)
    VHS, Kodak high grade T-120
  - Songs of Leonard Cohen- Last Holiday, undated; ID: 068.0147 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0147)
    VHS, TDK extra high grade
  - Eric Hoffer: the crowded life by Jeanne Wolf and Shep Morgan, undated; ID: 068.0148 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0148)
    VHS, 3M T-120
  - Moments Without Proper Names, Jeanne Wolf and Shep Morgan, undated; ID: 068.0149 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0149)
  - Playboy's Playmate Bloopers, undated; ID: 068.0150 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0150)
    VHS, 30 min
  - Interview of Edward Robb Ellis by Bill Dagg for Mutual Broadcasting System...Tues, June 30, 1970, ID: 068.0151 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0151)
    7 inch reel magnetic tape, Scotch brand, recorded at 7.5
  - New York, New York hosted by Arlene Francis, Guest Edward Robb Ellis. Broadcast, May 26, 1982, ID: 068.0152 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0152)
    7inch reel magnetic tape, unknown brand or length
  - Unlabeled, undated; ID: 068.0153 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0153)
    5 inch reel Scotch brand magnetic tape, 600 feet.
  - Jo and George Alley, Jerry Lord, Helen and Murray Lubell for the Ellises, undated; ID: 068.0154 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0154)
    5 inch reel, Pentron, 600 feet
  - Stutterer Harry Gordon hypnotized, undated; ID: 068.0155 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0155)
    5 inch reel, Scotch magnetic tape, 600 feet
  - Voice letter to Eddie and Ruth, undated; ID: 068.0156 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0156)
    7 inch reel, magnetic audiotape, 1250 feet.
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 1 and 2 of 7, undated; ID: 068.0157 and 068.0158 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0157 and 068.0158)
    5 inch reel, magnetic audiotape, unknown brand or length
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 3 and 4 of 7, undated; ID: 068.0159 and 068.0160 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0159 and 068.0160)
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reels 5 and 6 of 7, undated; ID: 068.0161 and 068.0162 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0161 and 068.0162)
  - Audio recording of A Nation in Torment reel 7 of 7, undated; ID: 068.0163 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0163)
  - Illegible label, two reels, undated; ID: 068.0164 and 068.0165 (Box 53, Media ID: 068.0164 and 068.0165)
    5 inch reel magnetic audiotape, Scotch brand, 600 feet
  - Mounted color transparencies featureing Edward Robb Ellis, Ruth Kraus Ellis, fireworks and cityscapes, undated (Box 53)
    Mounted color transparencies, number 120 film
- Oversize - Series I: Diary
  Oversize materials from Series I: Diary.
  - 1930-1942 (Box 40, Folder data_value_missing_a8a33de4eac3a362c43c12c6e1e4bc5b)
  - 1943-1948 (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_dc355d6cddf36437e3e25eff6760c79e)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 42, Folder data_value_missing_c336edfb38add704921ba343f51c4ffb)
  - 1951-Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder data_value_missing_f3e65b170809256969facb4224f90bd6)
- Oversize - Series II: Subject Files
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series II: Subject files. Contents are organized alphabetically by first letter.
  - Images, Undated (Box 44, Folder data_value_missing_1c64919af375527f9110698b7501ed9b)
  - Miscellaneous, including framed photographs, clippings and portraits, undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_548a2bbca4b82bba1786dae8a2fb92c7)
  - Portrait of Ruth, framed, undated (Box 46, Folder data_value_missing_ee9f3c34c62758f933cd4505e62fc9e0)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_d3a5e214372e1ea86253bf4085491606)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 48, Folder data_value_missing_e6a174f39487bc9a62ad3e5a37700b2d)
  - Promotion poster for Diary of a Century, undated (Box Map case, Folder data_value_missing_9cea334c8deb71540589a57a15b13143)
  - framed clipping, undated (Box Map case, Folder data_value_missing_4af0fe3209604c2184cae9f431c88292)
- Oversize - Series III: Book Typescripts
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series III: Book Typescripts. Contents are organized alphabetically by title.
  - Diary of a Century, Echoes of a Distant Thunder, undated (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_9eaab1594c34812a6440a68a4e2f97b8)